W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers, Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Water Resources, 1913-1978, undated; 2
  Series II. Water Resources, the largest series in the collection, contains reports, surveys, legal documents, and other literary productions pertaining to the development of Texas's water resources, both fresh and salt-water. Most of the materials are secondary in nature. Representative Poage did not contribute to them directly, rather, he would have used them for research purposes.
  The folders within this series are arranged alphabetically according to the creator of the materials, then chronologically under each creator. Publications from the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, the Texas Water Development Board, the U.S. Department of Agriculture, and the Soil Conservation Service are prominently featured. The series also includes several legal documents produced during a U.S. Supreme Court case, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, which debated ownership of the Texas tidelands and the oil resources therein. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - General, Scrapbook, “Brazos River Flood of December 1913, Angleton, Texas” (1 of 2), 1913-1944 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General, Scrapbook, “Brazos River Flood of December 1913, Angleton, Texas” (2 of 2), 1913-1944 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - General, “Comments from Interested Agencies: Bosque River Watershed, Texas”, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - General, “Comments from Interested Agencies: Little River Watershed, Texas”, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - General, Brief, “The Title to Texas Tide Lands”, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - General, “Comments from Interested Agencies: Brazos River Watershed, Texas”, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General, Brief, “Every State has Submerged Lands”, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - General, Clippings, Tidelands Fight, 1952 February (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General, Joint Report, “Water Developments and Potentialities of the State of Texas”, 1958 June (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - General, Joint Report, “Water Developments and Potentialities of the State of Texas”, 1958 July (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - General, Report, “Proposed Water Quality Criteria for Formulation of Texas Water Plan”, circa 1962 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - General, “Plan for Watershed Protection, Flood Prevention, and Recreation: Wet Walnut Creek Subwatershed No. 1”, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - General, Requests, Water Resource Projects, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, Paper, “Land and Water Resource Planning in Texas”, 1961 April 12 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Geological Society, Study, Hog Creek Watershed, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Bell-Milam Land and Water Rights Association, Brochure, “Development and Devastation?”, circa 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bosque Soil and Water Conservation District, Annual Report, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Electric Power Cooperative, Inc., “A Study of Power Costs at Source-Future Loads”, 1954 April 5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Electric Power Cooperative, Inc., “Summary of Negotiations on Interchange of Power in Lieu of North Texas Generation”, 1955 May 12 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Brazos Electric Power Cooperative, Inc., “Study of Fund Requirements and of Operating Feasibility for the Period 1965-1977” (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Bureau of Reclamation, Reports, “Reclamation Activity Highlights for Texas”, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Eliot Carter, Remarks, President Jimmy Carter’s Water Project, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Fish and Wildlife Service, Bulletin, “Gulf of Mexico: Its Origin, Waters, and Marine Life”, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Governor’s Committee on Water Conservation, Report, 1953 January 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - John W. Simmons, Address, “The Texas Water Problem”, 1957 March 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kansas State College of Agriculture and Applied Science, Circular, “Reducing Adverse Effects of Reservoirs”, 1952 October (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kaufman-Van Zandt-Rockwall Soil and Water Conservation District, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Millican Dam Development Association, Leaflet, “Facts About Millican Dam”, circa 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mission Water & Sewage Association, Pamphlet, “Water for Texas”, 1952 June 14 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Demonstration Water Project, Report, “Drinking Water Supplies in Rural America”, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Natural Resources Division, Research Committee, Houston Chamber of Commerce, Report, “Texas Natural Resources”, 1959 June (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Nolan-Aquilla Soil and Water Conservation District, Program and Plan, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - North Central Texas Council of Governments, Study, “Upper Trinity River Basin Comprehensive Sewerage Plan”, 1970 September (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pecos River Commission, Report, “Water Salvage and Salinity Alleviation Action Programs”, 1955 February (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Advisory Committee, Report, “Water Resources Policy”, 1955 December 22 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Roscoe Fleming, Article, “The Problem of Water”, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rural Electrification Administration, Press Release, Generation and Transmission Loan, 1965 June 11 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Senate Interim Committee on Tidelands, Report, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Soil Conservation Service, Memorandum, Salt Deposits in the Brazos River Basin, 1958 July 9 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Soil Conservation Service, Report, “Upstream Flood Prevention and Water Resources Development in the Brazos River Basin”, 1961 February (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Soil Conservation Service, Packet, “Material on Upstream Watershed Protection and Flood Prevention”, 1963, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Soil Conservation Service, Report, “Soil and Water Conservation on the High Plains of Texas”, 1969 July (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Soil Conservation Service, “Work Plan for Watershed Protection, Flood Prevention, and Agricultural and Non-Agricultural Water Management, Paluxy River Watershed”, 1972 January (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Soil Conservation Service, “Final Environmental Impact Statement: Elm Creek Watershed Project”, 1975 July (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Soil Conservation Service, “Environmental Impact Statement: Wet Walnut Creek Watershed”, 1976 April (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Soil Conservation Service, “Watershed Plan and Environmental Impact Statement: Deposit Watershed for Broome, Chenango, and Delaware Counties, New York”, 1977 September (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Hydrology Inter-Agency Committee on Water Resources, “Inventory of Published and Unpublished Chemical Analyses of Surface Waters in Western United States, 1947-1955”, 1956 September (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Texas A&M University, Bulletin, “Water Evaporation Studies in Texas”, 1954 November (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Texas A&M University, Speeches on “Water for Texas”, 1955 September (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Texas A&M University, Proceedings of the 2nd Annual Conference, “Water for Texas”, 1956 September 17-19 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Texas A&M University, Proceedings of the 12th Annual Conference, “Water for Texas”, 1967 November 20-21 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Texas A&M University, Annual Report, Water Resources Institute, 1969 July (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Texas A&M University, Summary Report, “Texas Water Resources Institute”, 1971 June (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Texas A&M University, Study, “Water Resource Uses and Issues in Texas”, 1978 August (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Texas A&M University, Newsletter, Texas Water Resources, 1978 December (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Texas Agricultural Experiment Station, Report, “Flood Plain Management”, 1976 November (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Texas Historical Commission, Report, “Archeological Surveys in the Tehuacana Creek Watershed Hill and McLennan Counties, Texas”, 1976 September (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Texas Natural Resources Council, Report, “Texas Coastal Natural Resources Issues”, 1978 June (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Texas Society of Professional Engineers, Report, “Water!”, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Texas State Teachers Association, “The Annexation Agreement Between the United States and Texas”, 1949 October (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Texas Water Development Board, Brochure, “Water for Texas”, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Texas Water Development Board, Report, “Water for Texas: A Plan for the Future”, 1966 May (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Brazos River Basin”, 1966 June (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Neches River Basin”, 1966 June (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Neches-Trinity Coastal Basin”, 1966 June (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Red River Basin”, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the San Jacinto River Basin”, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the San Jacinto-Brazos Coastal Basin”, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Trinity River Basin”, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Trinity-San Jacinto Coastal Basin”, 1966 June (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Colorado River Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Colorado-Lavaca Coastal Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Guadalupe River Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Lavaca River Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Lavaca-Guadalupe Coastal Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Nueces River Basin”, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Nueces-Rio Grande Coastal Basin”, 1966 July (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the San Antonio River Basin”, 1966 July (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the San Antonio-Nueces Coastal Basin”, 1966 July (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Canadian River Basin”, 1966 August (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Texas Water Development Board, “A Summary of the Preliminary Plan for Proposed Water Resources Development in the Rio Grande Basin”, 1966 August (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Texas Water Development Board, Draft, “Continuing Water Resources Planning and Development for Texas, Volume 2” (1 of 3), 1977 May (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Texas Water Development Board, Draft, “Continuing Water Resources Planning and Development for Texas, Volume 2” (2 of 3), 1977 May (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Texas Water Development Board, Draft, “Continuing Water Resources Planning and Development for Texas, Volume 2” (3 of 3), 1977 May (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Texas Water Resources Institute, Pamphlet, “More Than a Drop in the Bucket”, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Texas Water Rights Commission, Report, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Texas Water Rights Commission, Report, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Tidelands, Article, “The Tidelands Case”, Oil Newsmagazine, 1949 December (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Tidelands, Essay, “Tidelands: State's Rights”, 1952 March (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Trinity Improvement Association, Booklet, The Program for Flood Control and the Prevention of Soil Erosion in the Trinity River Watershed, circa 1944 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Trinity River Project, “Status Report of Environmental Evaluations, Main Text” (1 of 2), 1975 June (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Trinity River Project, “Status Report of Environmental Evaluations, Main Text” (2 of 2), 1975 June (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Trinity River Project, “Status Report of Environmental Evaluations, Appendix A”, 1975 June (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Trinity River Project, “Status Report of Environmental Evaluations, Appendix B” (1 of 2), 1975 June (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Trinity River Project, “Status Report of Environmental Evaluations, Appendix B” (2 of 2), 1975 June (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Interim Report on Brazos River, Covering Leon River, Texas” (1 of 2), 1946 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Interim Report on Brazos River, Covering Leon River, Texas” (2 of 2), 1946 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 1, 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 2, 1947 August 15 (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 3 (1 of 2), 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 3 (2 of 2), 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 4 (1 of 2), 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 4 (2 of 2), 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 5, 1947 August 15 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 6, 1947 August 15 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Report on Survey of Brazos River and Tributaries, Texas, Oyster Creek, Texas, Jones Creek, Texas”, Volume 7, 1947 August 15 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Whitney Dam and Reservoir: Bill of Materials for Construction of Powerhouse and Switchyard”, 1951 January (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, "Whitney Dam and Reservoir: Conduit and Cable Schedule for Construction of Powerhouse and Switchyard", 1951 January (Box 33 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, "Whitney Dam and Reservoir: Plans for Construction of Powerhouse and Switchyard", 1951 January (Box 33 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, "Whitney Dam and Reservoir: Reinforcement Bar Details for Construction of Powerhouse and Switchyard", 1951 January (Box 33 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Whitney Dam and Reservoir: Specifications for Construction of Powerhouse and Switchyard”, 1951 January (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Conference Proceedings, 1951 March 9 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, House Document #535, “Brazos River and Tributaries, Oyster Creek, and Jones Creek, Texas”, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Water Resources Development by the Corps of Engineers in Texas”, 1955 January (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Water Resources Development by the Corps of Engineers in Texas”, 1957 January (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Press Release, Civil Works Program, 1957 January 16 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Pamphlet, “Waco Dam and Reservoir (Under Construction)”, 1959 August (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Water Resources Development by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers in Texas”, 1969 January (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 1 (1 of 3), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 1 (2 of 3), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 1 (3 of 3), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 2 (1 of 2), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 2 (2 of 2), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 3, 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 4, 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 5 (1 of 2), 1973 September (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 5 (2 of 2), 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 6 (1 of 2), 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 6 (2 of 2), 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 7 (1 of 2), 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Volume 7 (2 of 2), 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Report, “Wastewater Management Plan: Colorado River and Tributaries, Texas”, Summary, 1973 September (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Navigability Study, Brazos River, Tributaries and Lakes, Brazos River Basin, Texas and New Mexico” (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Navigability Study, Brazos River, Tributaries and Lakes, Brazos River Basin, Texas and New Mexico” (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Belton Dam Preliminary Feasibility Report: Adding Hydropower to Belton Dam” (1 of 2), 1976 February (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, “Belton Dam Preliminary Feasibility Report: Adding Hydropower to Belton Dam” (2 of 2), 1976 February (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Publication, “Water Resources Development”, 1977 January (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Little River Watershed, Texas”, 1948 September (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, Report, “Missouri River Basin Agricultural Program”, 1949 April (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Bosque River Watershed, Texas”, 1950 July (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Bosque River Watershed, Texas”, Appendices (1 of 2), 1950 July (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Bosque River Watershed, Texas”, Appendices (2 of 2), 1950 July (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Little River Watershed, Texas”, 1950 July (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, “Interim Survey Report on the Brazos River and Tributaries for the Little River Watershed, Texas”, Appendices, 1950 July (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, Leaflet, “Know Your Watersheds”, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, “Reconnaissance Report on Upper Brazos River Basin, Texas”, 1941 November (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Report, “Demineralization of Saline Waters”, 1952 October (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Annual Report, “Saline Water Conversion”, 1955 January (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Report, “Elements of the Texas Water Problem”, 1957 January (Box 32 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Paper, “Saline-Water Resources of Texas”, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Booklet, Natural Resources of Texas, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Geological Survey, “Water Resources Data for Texas”, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, Geological Survey, “Water Resources Investigations in Texas”, 1977 February (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Department of the Interior, “Report on the Water Conservation Opportunities Study”, 1978 September (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - U.S. House Judiciary Committee, Report, Submerged Lands Act, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - U.S. House Judiciary Committee, Hearings, Submerged Lands, 1953 February-March (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, Bill, H.R. 4198, Submerged Lands Act, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, Memorandum, H.R. 6112, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Hearings, Submerged Lands, 1949 October 4-10 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Hearings, Submerged Lands, 1951 March-April (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Statement by Harold Fatzer, Submerged Lands, 1953 February 16 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Study Commission-Texas, Report, “Part 1: The Commission Plan”, 1962 March (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Study Commission-Texas, Report, “Part 2: Resources and Problems”, 1962 March (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Study Commission-Texas, Report, “Part 3: The Eight Basins”, 1962 March (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Study Commission-Texas, Report, “Summary and Recommendations”, 1962 April (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Legal Documents, U.S.A. v. State of Louisiana, 1948 October-1950 October (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Brief and Petition, U.S.A. v. State of California, 1949 September-October (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Motion of the State of Texas to Dismiss the Complaint of the United States, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1948 October (Box 30, Folder 6)